{
    "subject": "resource/K._J._Stevens",
    "predicate": "ontology/genre",
    "object": "resource/Fiction",
    "human_readable": "The genre of K.J. Stevens' work is Fiction.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9438393115997314,
            "question": "What makes K.J. Stevens' work categorized as Fiction?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.804452657699585,
            "question": "Are there any subgenres within Fiction that K.J. Stevens might write in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7612541317939758,
            "question": "Could you give me an example of a fictional work by K.J. Stevens?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7016766667366028,
            "question": "Is K.J. Stevens known for writing non-fiction?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.646912157535553,
            "question": "What genre does K.J. Stevens write in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5641589164733887,
            "question": "What types of stories might K.J. Stevens tell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4179481565952301,
            "question": "Would you expect to find realistic events in K.J. Stevens' books?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.205572709441185,
            "question": "How does the genre of Fiction influence a reader's expectations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20277462899684906,
            "question": "What are some popular characteristics of Fiction?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08258175849914551,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the elements typically found in fictional stories?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The genre of K.J. Stevens' work is Fiction.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7744_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular characteristics of Fiction?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7744_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the genre of Fiction influence a reader's expectations?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7744_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Would you expect to find realistic events in K.J. Stevens' books?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7744_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7744_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7744_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7744_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7744_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7744_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7744_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7744_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7744_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7744_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7744_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple, as it mentions that K.J. Stevens has written fiction, including a collection of fiction and nonfiction (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7744/re-ranker-msmarco/59.txt) and a novel \"Pilgrims Bay\" which is described as his first novel."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about K.J. Stevens as an American novelist and short story writer, mentioning that his first novel \"Pilgrims Bay\" was released in 2007 under the category of Fiction. This supports the statement that the genre of K.J. Stevens' work is Fiction."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}